JESSICA J. MONTERO

WEB DEVELOPER + TECHNICAL & ONPAGE SEO

I have over 4 years of experience developing and managing websites projects, from their conception through to implementation, maintaining approach on SEO and analytics web for after the merge provides all the tools to the Marketing and Sales team.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer + SEO Technical and On-page

Working in the Redwoods

May 2020 - Apr 2021

Ecommerce Website

Web Designer + SEO On-page Secartys | CICAT | SmartTech | Solartys

Apr 2019 - May 2020 Corporate Websites

Web Designer + SEO On-page Lola de Miguel

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018 Personal Brand Website

Web Designer + SEO On-page Terractiva

Dic 2017 - Feb 2018 Corporate Web

EDUCATION

React JS Course

Feb - **Currently attending** 2022 IT Academy, BCN Activa

UX / UI

Mar 2022

Udemy

Bootcamp Full Stack Developer

Jul - Oct 2021

Aulab Academy

Google Analytics

Nov - 2020 | ID 61974930

Technical Degree in International Trade

2012-2014

Centre Lopez Vicuña · BCN

TECHNICAL SKILLS

FRONTEND

 $\mathsf{HTML5} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{CSS} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{CSS} \, \mathsf{Grid} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{CSS} \, \mathsf{Flexbox} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{Sass} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{JavaScript} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{Git} \, \cdot \, \mathsf{GitHub}$

















WEB DESIGN

Figma · Visual Composer · WordPress · WooCommerce · Mailchimp











SEO & ANALYTICS

Screaming Frog · Yoast SEO · G Search Console · G Analytics · G Tag Manager











PORTFOLIO

https://jessica-j-montero.github.io/tech-portfolio/

CONTACT

+34 653 573 982

holajjmontero@gmail.com 08037 Barcelona

